Look! I drew you, Aria!
I don't want me!
Draw Meria instead!
Aww, but I worked hard on that...
You know she'd much rather get a picture of
her favorite character from your manga.
She's VB's biggest fan, after all.
Mami!
You've still got lots of copies left.
Go sign a few more for her.
Why bother?
It got canceled because
no one was reading it.
Do you think she cares about that? Hmm?
It's so cool!
I loved my dad and his manga.
But...
When are you actually going
to get published again?
You've told me a thousand times
"this next meeting is the one!"
But it's a year later,
and we're still here!
That last one got shot down.
I'm working on something new now.
What?!
Why didn't you bother telling me that?!
It wouldn't have meant anything to you.
It means something when I'm paying the bills!
Long story short,
he just couldn't get published again,
and they got divorced when I was six.
I get why my mom left him.
The last thing I remember about
my dad was his obsession with work.
So, I'm not bothered they got divorced.
Mom and Dad had their reasons.
What bothers me is the last
words we said to each other...
...were said in anger.
Why are you reading my manga?
Don't you know it's horrible?!
Give it back!
You don't get it, Aria.
Everyone says this manga is trash.
Everyone pointed and
laughed at how awful it was!
How no one should ever bother with it!
Everyone said it.
The editorial team agreed...
That was that.
This book is the proof I'm a hack job manga-ka!
This stupid book is the reason...
...that my career is dead!
You...
I hate you, and I hate your stupid manga!
I couldn't have known that was
the day my dad was leaving us.
Comrades in (Cosplay) Arms
It's been ten years since he left.
Mom says she doesn't know what he's up to.
Though I can bet he probably quit working on manga.
I would've never guessed Aria's dad was
the creator of Valkyrie Battle, Yo Kisaki...
I've always wanted to apologize for what I said.
And I want him to apologize, too.
So you're doing this to find Kisaki-sensei...
I mean, your dad?
I have no idea where he is or what he's up to.
So if I got famous, he'd see me,
but my dad doesn't watch TV or read magazines.
But, if I wore a cosplay from
a manga he created,
he'd have to hear about me!
I thought about hiring a private investigator,
but I wasn't sure what
I'd do when I found him.
Private Investigator
I don't feel like having that talk with him right now.
But there's one thing I want to tell him,
more than anything.
I want to tell the creator of Valkyrie Battle
how much I really love his manga.
Because I'm not just his daughter.
I'm a reader and a fan of his manga.
You want to show the creator
how much you love his work?
I never needed to teach
you anything about cosplay.
You already know what cosplay is!
Ririsa...
I've got nothing to teach you, Aria-chan!
We'll help!
You want to get super famous, right?!
We can help!
Nono-pi...
First you have to get famous,
then you can do a VB cosplay, yeah?
What event should we target?
If we're doing Ariel,
maybe we should aim for July?
August?
Please! We've gotta do it for Summer Comiket!
Summer Comiket?!
So, everyone's kinda freaking out...
Is that a big deal?
You haven't heard of Summer Comiket?!
It's the biggest event of the year!
Seven hundred thousand people go there!
Seven hundred thousand?
O-okay...
If I post that Liliel and I are doing
the Angelic Airborne Defense Squadron...
Wait a second...
We're gonna need one more person!
Everyone will think we'll be a group of four!
Oh, the girl with the black hair.
The one who kinda came out of nowhere, honestly...
It seems like that in the spinoff!
She's actually a super popular
character from the original!
Should we start looking for our fourth?
So actually, I had this thought when
we were discussing plans earlier.
She should be coming today, too.
Huh?
Senpai!
Guess whose modeling work's
going on hiatus for a little bit?
Wait, who are all these other girls?!
M-M-Mi...
What?
Why do I have a bad feeling about this?
Mikarin?!
You wanna introduce yourself?!
Ohmigod, I'm such a huge fan!
Wait, you're a fan?
I'm Aria! I follow your Insta,
and I always read your interviews!
Wow, Mikari, you really are famous.
This is so cool.
Thanks, Aria-chan.
Want an autograph?
Thanks for all the support.
Ohmigod, you're gorgeous...
Yay!
So... Who is she?
You don't know Mikarin?! She's a huge model!
Weren't you the one who told me
to be a model to get famous?
So... Maybe your original plan was the right choice.
Okay, I understand what's up now.
Okumura and Mikarin were
friends when they were kids?!
So you need me to be your fourth member.
Sure, but even if you're friends with Ririsa,
there's no way you'd actually do it, right?
If Senpai asked, I'd at least think it over.
Huh?
No way?! You'd do it for HIM?!
Wait, how is he standing in the same room
as Mikarin and not freaking out?!
Senpai...
D'ya wanna see me cosplay?
I get to see all four members of the squad together?!
Hell yeah!
You're that obsessed with anime girls?!
Then I'm in!
Mikarin?!
This is good and all,
but are you sure?
Fashion models don't usually go to Comiket...
Wait, Mikarin said in an interview that
cosplay is one of her hobbies!
Huh?!
She's been posting cosplay pics to her Insta, too!
Yep! My agency said it's cool for me to cosplay.
Really?!
Well, yeah.
What do you like to do on your days off?
I love to cosplay!
Cosplay? Wow.
For two months,
I've put everything I have into making
it normal for models to cosplay!
Now, it'll be a cinch for me to wear a costume,
and I'm doing it all for one special person...
Did you do that for me?
Girl, no.
Anyways, I'll wear whatever Senpai wants,
just say the word.
We could book a private studio
and take some raunchy pics, too...
You'd do that? Thanks.
Wait, does Mikarin have a thing for Okumura?!
No way, that'd be crazy.
Look how close they are after
so many years of friendship...
That's so cool.
Okay, then!
Let's get started on making the
costumes for Ariel and Miriela!
Yay!
I bought the materials you asked for.
Do you need any for Miriela?
I already got them, boss!
Okay, could you get out the pattern paper?
I'm gonna start with teaching
you how to make your own pattern!
Is this it?
Wait, you're gonna sew, too?
Just let Ririsa do everything.
No way!
Making it by hand will really show my love!
That's why I make all my Valentine's
chocolate and write physical letters, too!
Wait, did Senpai not realize I loved him because
I always gave him super-expensive chocolate?
This cost me ten thousand yen from a fancy hotel.
Cool.
No, that wasn't the problem.
But, I can solve it by doing this next year.
This cost me ten thousand yen from a fancy hotel.
I followed your instructions
and got my measurements.
Are you not gonna do mine?
Nope! I remember all of yours from last time!
Wait, but like, that was back in May.
I could've grown a little since then!
I do all my exercises every day,
and I've been taking supplements!
In just two months, though?
Manga Club
Measurement Time
See? Same numbers as before!
I'll start on your pattern!
But I did the exercises... Why?
I-it's okay...
I feel like we're bonding.
A pattern is made up of each piece of
fabric we're going to cut and sew.
We'll determine the shapes of all the
pieces and how they'll get sewn together.
None of these instructions are in the manga,
so we have to figure it out on our own.
Taking the 2D design and recreating it in
3D is where a cosplayer's skill can really shine!
We can use most of Liliel's pattern to make Ariel,
so just follow along with me!
This is Version 4.6.2!
I added darts to the bust so you
don't have to use a push-up bra anymore!
I also used Mayura's two-layered craft technique
to recreate her "impossible" boot design!
Everything okay?
Nah, like, listening to all these details made
me realize how wrong I was doing it before.
I kinda feel embarrassed I even called that cosplay.
You don't need to feel embarrassed!
This isn't the "right" way to do it, Aria-chan.
I just want you to see how fun it is to
recreate a character you really love!
So just make it about love...
That's right!
What do you like so much about Ariel?
That's easy!
I love how she fights for her friends!
Meria from VB is the same way!
I love girls who care about friendship.
That's why I always want to make
new friends and get to know them!
Wait, so manga is why she turned into a gyaru?!
Can that even happen?
Otaku, gyaru, and delinquents
may all share a common ancestor...
Class Outcasts
That's it, good!
Now connect it up...
You're doing great!
I dunno, really?
Hey, Senpai! Are you listening? Senpai!
The base for your top is finished!
Let's have you try it on
Hey, Senpai! Are you listening? Senpai!
before we sew everything together.
Sorry, I'm slowing things down!
I have nothing to do anyway,
so I'll just head home!
No way! Just chill here, god!
That's right!
Your presence gives us
so much more motivation!
Seriously, what makes him so special?
If you talking is hard for you, I can wait.
He's a good person.
Together, we'll make it happen!
I can kind of imagine what happened.
I'm sure they've had their own moments.
I'm sure he's shown them he's trustworthy.
I'm gonna sit outside and replay
Episode 13 in my head.
Him, though?
Manga Club
Fitting Time
It fits like a glove!
Wait, I'm looking closer,
and it even has the same folds
in the fabric we saw in the anime!
It's hella accurate!
Is anyone gonna notice that tiny detail, though?
What do you think, Senpai?
Whoa, you've got the same fabric folds, too!
Okay, then!
I messed up again!
I keep messing up the stitches
and the pleats are all over the place.
This sucks so bad!
Yeah, pleated skirts are really tough.
And you can't redo stitches on stretch
PVC so it's back to square one...
I'm trapped in stretch PVC hell!
I'm trapped in
stretch PVC hell!
I'm so bad at this. I can't do it right.
I'm like, never gonna be as good as you.
It's okay!
Just keep persevering,
and the pleats will eventually be done!
I don't wanna persevere...
Hey Ririsa, how long do
I have to keep this on for?
I totally forgot!
Senpai left to catch that anime at 6,
so maybe I should head out, too.
I'm hungry!
Wanna grab dinner at a restaurant together?
My mom's gonna be home late.
That sounds great!
Want to come with, Mikari-chan?
Dinner together with friends?!
Sure, I guess.
I can check that off my Friend Wishlist!
I love when there's a tablet so
I don't have to talk to the waiter...
W-what do you all want?
What're you getting, Nono-pi?
You don't normally eat that much.
Omu! Omurice!
I can eat an entire plate of omurice by myself!
Beef Stew Omurice
Omurice has saved my life time and time again!
What are you getting, Aria-chan?!
I'm still frustrated from earlier,
so I'm getting tandoori
chicken with Mexican pilaf.
Make that extra pilaf.
That's 1300 Calories... what does she eat in a day?
1300 Calories
I'll have a chicken salad and an acai yogurt.
You're on a model's diet!
How about you, Ririsa-chan?
Oh, I found a super-cheap combo I can order!
You're all about cost!
Evening combo mixed grill with extra rice,
a side of fries, salad and endless drink refills.
Then extra sides of corn potage and bread rolls,
and a jumbo strawberry parfait for dessert!
C-can I order some anmitsu?
She went for it!
I have a question.
Ririsa-chan, you make cosroms, right?
With all our prep for the group cosplay,
are you gonna be able to make a ROM for Comiket?
Or did you not get a spot?
Oh, actually...
When I went to Winter Comiket,
I didn't even grab an application for summer.
Really?
I mean, back then...
Can I get your new Liliel doujin?!
I couldn't have even imagined I'd be here now...
Preparing to go to Summer Comiket
with friends in a group cosplay!
Ririsa-chan was just like me...
F-friends?
I mean, I guess you could call us that.
That's right!
We're going to cosplay together, as friends!
Meria and Ariel fought hard for their friends!
I can't give up!
I'm going to become them,
just like Ririsa does!
I'm going to persevere for my friends!
That's it, that's it!
You're doing perfect so far, Aria-chan!
So... You have to start over again?
Give her a little time to process it emotionally...
You're almost there...
That's right.
Stop the needle...
I'm done! With just the skirt, but still!
Aria-chan, you did so good!
Great job!
You've really been putting in effort!
I gotta try it on!
Aria-chan, Okumura-senpai is-
Gone!
Manga Club
Your eyes are rather slow.
He left faster than the speed of sound...
Like a true hero.
It's perfect!
Okay, where's mine?
Don't worry! I've been working on it at home!
What?! When the hell do you sleep?!
Gotta get that fabric...
Never mind.
Nono-pi, how do I look?
Really good! This part looks great!
How'd you manage it?
Manga Club
A lot of sweat, blood, and tears!
Okay, see you later, girls!
Tomorrow, we start putting on the finishing touches!
I'm home!
Kisaki residence, who's calling?
She's on the phone?
My mother-in-law? Please.
Dad's mom called?!
We haven't been family for a long time.
What do you want?
Look, it doesn't matter...
He died years ago.
Destiny